Hello and good morning everyone. So
today is the second trading session of
this week. So let's get started with
today's top stocks and news. The first
one is ISA credential company reported
the quarter 4 numbers whereas AP is
reported at uh 3502 crores. It is down
by 3.1% on yearly basis. Value of new
business is up by 2.5%. Value of new
business margins are reported at 22.7%
versus 21.5% on yearly basis. Also the
company declares final dividend
of85 pesa per share. The next share is
ISA Lombard because company's net profit
is down by 1.2% at 509 crores. Gross
premium of the company's up by 10.2%.
Operating profit is again down by 26%.
Also the underwriting loss is reported
at 209 crores versus the loss of 235
crores. combined ratio is reported at
102 uh 102.5% versus
102.3% on yearly basis. The next stock
is IRA because company's net profit is
up by approximately 49% at 501 crores.
Net interest income of the company is
again up by 47.3% at 801 crores. Revenue
is uh reported at 1,905 crores which is
up by 37% on yearly basis and margins
are reported at 31.01 01% which is
substantially contracted versus 33.92%
on Y and Y basis. The next stock which
you need to look at is Indent bank
because company receives report from the
external agency and company report
identifies disparency in the derivative
deals has quantified negative impact of
1,979 crores also assesses adverse
impact of 2.27% to net worth of the
Indesen bank. it is going to reflect in
fiscal year 25 financial statement. Now
the bank will continue to take suitable
step to augment internal controls
relating to the derivative account
operation of the bank. Also uh you need
to look at because bank's internal
review estimated an inverse impact of
around 2.35% of net worth as of December
2024. The next stock is Mahanagar gas
because there's a APM gas allocation for
company reduced by 18% effective from
16th of April which is today. Also the
reduction of APM volumes has been
replaced with uh new well intervention
gas. Now the Mahanagar gas says that
that reduction in APM APM gas allocation
to have adverse impact on company's
profitability and the company is in
process of exploring all measures to
mitigate the impact. The next stock is
Indra Gas because domestic gas
allocation for IGL has been reduced by
20% effective from today. The company
has been allocated an additional 125% of
the reduced volume as of new well gas
also. Now the Indra is saying this
revision in allocation is expected to
impact the company's profitability. The
next stock which you need to look at is
oil India because company secures 9
block under OALP round 9. This adds over
approximately 51,000 square kilometer to
oil India exploration portfolio. With
this, oil India's exploration sage grows
by 85% to 1.10 lakh square kilometer
from 60,000 square kilometers. The next
stock is NHPC because company declares
commercial operation of unit 3 200
megawatt of Pariati second H project in
Himal Pradesh. you need to look at
because company also declared commercial
operation of unit one, unit one and
three of Pariati 2 H project on April
1st. The next which you need to look at
is Estradm Healthcare because CCI
approved merger of quality care India uh
into company by the way of scheme of
amalgamation. Post merger company will
be renamed as Estradm control quality
limited. Prior to the merger, Astral
shall buy 5% stake in quality care from
BCP Asia and Sentella Morish Norish's
holding. Now the quality gear it's
existing shareholding Sentella BCP and
certain minority shareholder are
proposed to hold certain stake in the
merged entity. The next stock which you
need to look at is Vanta because Karen
oil and gas acquire seven new block in
OP round 9. OLP is basically open sage
licensing policy and also awarded block
comprise of four onshore and three
shallow water blocks located in
hydrocarbon basin of Cam Bay and Bombay.
So these were some of the stock which
you need to look at in today's trading
session. Thank you. Bye-bye.